A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, New York Office, Series 22 FA365
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appointments Office, 1959-1965; 1; 9 Cubic Feet
  - Regrets, December 1962 (Box 11, Folder 357)
    1. Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) Conference 2. National Convention of Home Builders 3. State of Israel Bond Committee
  - New York, New York, January 6, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 358)
    1. Salem Methodist Church
  - Albany, New York, January 8, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 359)
    1. Dinner with Republican members of the Senate
  - New York, New York, January 11, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 360)
    1. New York Stock Exchange Luncheon 2. United Cerebral Palsy Humanitarian Award
  - Albany, New York, January 15, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 361)
    1. New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum
  - Albany, New York, January 16, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 362)
  - New York, New York, January 17, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 363)
    1. Dedication of Alexander Hamilton Bridge 2. Dedication of George Washington Bus Station
  - New York, New York, January 24, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 364)
    1. Westchester County Republican Dinner
  - New York, New York, January 25, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 365)
    1. Citizen's Council on Traffic Safety
  - New York, New York, January 25, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 366)
    1. Federation of Women's Republican Clubs (Carl Spad speech, NAR did not attend)
  - New York, New York, January 26, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 367)
    1. Women's National Republican Club
  - Albany, New York, January 29, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 368)
    1. New York State Publishers Association
  - New York, New York, January 30, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 369)
    1. Republican Victory Dinner
  - New York, New York, January 31, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 370)
    1. Advisory Council on HIgher Education
  - Regrets, January 1963 (Box 12, Folder 371)
    1. B'nai B'rith Covenant Breakfast 2. Association of Chief School Administrators 3. White Plains Council of Community Services 4. Hospital of Jacques Loewe Association 5. Meeting with 16 Eagle Scouts 6. Mr. Donald S. Underhill
  - Newark, New Jersey, February 2, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 372)
    1. Republican Legislators Fund Raising Dinner
  - Albany, New York, February 4, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 373)
    1. American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Legislative Conference
  - Albany, New York; New York, New York, February 5, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 374)
    Albany (AM) 1. Legislators Breakfast, Executive Mansion New York City 1. Association of Towns of the State of New York 2. Association of Fire Districts, State of New York Albany (PM) 1. Empire State Chamber of Commerce
  - Washington, DC, February 6, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 375)
    1. Dinner at the Army-Navy Club
  - Chicago, Illinois, February 9, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 376)
    1. Meeting with Republican State Chairman 2. Press conference 3. 1963 Lincoln Day Dinner
  - Albany, New York, February 10, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 377)
    1. Visit by Marian Anderson (comments by NAR on memo)
  - Albany, New York, February 11, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 378)
    1. General Electric Public Affairs Meeting
  - New York, New York, February 12, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 379)
    1. New York County Lincoln Day Dinner 2. Brooklyn - Kings County Lincoln Day Dinner
  - Brooklyn, New York, February 14, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 380)
    1. Ground breaking of Research Hospital
  - Albany, New York, February 18, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 381)
    1. Business and Professional Women's Clubs
  - Albany, New York, February 19, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 382)
    1. American Legion Legislative Dinner
  - New York, New York, February 22, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 383)
    1. Dinner with Venezuelan President and Mrs. Romulo Betancourt
  - Albany, New York, February 25, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 384)
  - Wilmington, Delaware, February 27, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 385)
  - New York, New York, February 28, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 386)
    1. Reception with Belgain Trade Mission
  - Regrets, February 1963 (Box 12, Folder 387)
    1. Present Eagle Scout Medal 2. Yorktown Republican Club 3. Interfaith Movement Dinner 4. Rowing Club of Syracuse University
  - New York, New York, March 2, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 388)
    1. Inner Circle Dinner
  - Albany, New York, March 3, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 389)
    1. Dinner in honor of Doctor Hilleboe
  - Albany, New York, March 5, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 390)
    1. State Conference of National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Branches
  - New York, New York, March 6, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 391)
    1. New York Building Congress
  - New York, New York; Farmingdale, New York; Albany, New York, March 7, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 392)
    New York City 1. Opening of new Pan Am Building Farmingdale 1. Advisory Council for the Advancement of Industrial Research and Development Albany 1. Civil Service Employees Association
  - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, March 9, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 393)
    1. Press conference 2. Luncheon with local leaders 3. Meeting with State Executive Committee 4. Young Republican Reception 5. State Finance Committee Fund Raising Dinner
  - Albany, New York, March 12, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 394)
    1. Republican Women of the Legislature 2. Testimonial Dinner for Louis J. Lefkowitz
  - New York, New York, March 14, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 395)
  - Albany, New York, March 15, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 396)
    1. Rules Committee Reception
  - New York, New York; Albany, New York, March 16, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 397)
    New York City 1. St. Patrick's Day Parade (reviewing stand) Albany 1. Legislative Correspondents Association
  - Albany, New York, March 18, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 398)
    1. Society of Foreign Consuls, dinner at mansion
  - Albany, New York, March 19, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 399)
    1. Westchester County Legislators
  - Syracuse, New York, March 25, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 400)
    1. County Officers Association 2. Press conference
  - New York, New York, March 30, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 401)
    1. Dinner at the French Consulate General with General Louis Joxe
  - Regrets, March 1963 (Box 13, Folder 402)
    1. Drug and Hospital Employees Union 2. American Eaglets 3. The Elmer Award Dinner 4. Barrister's Ball 5. Manhattan Republican Club 6. Grand Council Columbia Associations
  - New York, New York, April 1, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 403)
    1. American Council for the International Promotion of Democracy Under God
  - New York, New York, April 2, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 404)
    1. Rockefeller Foundation 50th Anniversary
  - New York, New York, April 4, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 405)
    1. American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Dinner (marked "regret")
  - Topeka, Kansas, April 5, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 406)
    1. Kansas Federation of Republican Women 2. Republican State Committee Meeting 3. Reception, Dinner, "The Republican Crusade"
  - Omaha, Nebraska, April 6, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 407)
    1. Press conference 2. Luncheon 3. Executive Committee Meeting 4. Senator Hruska Appreciation Dinner
  - Washington, DC, April 10, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 408)
    1. Congressional Breakfast for Republicans
  - New York, New York, April 17, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 409)
    1. International Radio and Television Society 2. Governor's Council on Children and Youth
  - New York, New York, April 19, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 410)
    1. Luncheon for General Douglas MacArthur
  - New York, New York, April 20, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 411)
    1. National Federation of Young Republican Clubs
  - New York, New York, April 21, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 412)
    1. Directors of the Associated Press
  - Albany, New York, April 23, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 413)
    1. Unveiling of models of South Mall Project
  - New York, New York, April 25, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 414)
    1. American Newspaper Publishers Association
  - Hamilton County, Ohio, April 29, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 415)
    1. Press conference 2. 1963 Republican Dinner
  - Regrets, April 1963 (Box 13, Folder 416)
    1. Westchester Outdoor Art Exhibit 2. Dinner in honor of Dr. Edler Hawkins 3. Reception in honor of Bunny Lasker 4. 150th Anniversary of Battle of York 5. Auburn Community College 6. Advertising Club of New York 7. Automobile Dealers of New York 8. Men's Club of Riverdale 9. The Municipal Forum of New York 10. Grand Council Columbia Associations
  - New York, New York; Garden City, New York, May 2, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 417)
    New York City 1. Governor's Conference on Aging 2. Community Blood Council of Greater New York Garden City 1. Adelphi College 2. Nassau County Republican Committee
  - New York, New York, May 6, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 418)
    1. 40th Anniversary of "Time"
  - Washington, DC, May 9, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 419)
    1. Dinner in honor of Senator Barry Goldwater
  - Regrets, May 1963 (Box 13, Folder 420)
    1. Rotary Club of Ballston Spa 2. Westchester Outdoor Art Exhibit 3. Institute of Puerto Rico 4. Kansas City Art Institute and School of Design 5. Law Day, USA 6. Advertising Club of New York 7. The Fifty American Artists 8. Willoughby House Settlement 9. American Legion Post, Yorktown 10. Kiwanis Club of San Diego 11. Industrial and Engineering Exhibition 12. Mayor's Day Proclamation
  - Albany, New York, June 3, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 421)
    1. Citizens Planning Committee
  - New York, New York, June 5, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 422)
    1. New York City Cancer Society
  - New York, New York, June 6, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 423)
  - Tarrytown, New York, June 10, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 424)
    1. Dedication of Chevrolet and Fisher Body Plants 2. Luncheon, Tappan Hill Restaurant
  - Albany, New York, June 11, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 425)
    1. New York State Personnel Council
  - Rockland County, New York, June 12, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 426)
    1. Nyack - Rockland County Republican Women, tea 2. New City - Rockland County Committee Dinner
  - Buffalo, New York, June 13, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 427)
    1. Ashford Atomic Reprocessing Plant 2. Manufacturers and Traders Trust Company
  - Garden City, New York; Bronx, New York, June 15, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 428)
    Garden City 1. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Bronx 1. Bronx County Republican County Committee
  - Oswego, New York, June 21, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 429)
    1. Port of Oswego New Wharf and Terminal 2. Tour of Alroll Plant
  - New York, New York; Lido Beach, New York, June 27, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 430)
    New York City 1. United Jewish Appeal Luncheon Lido Beach 1. The Joseph F. Carlino Scholarship Fund Dinner
  - Upstate New York, June 28, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 431)
    1. Lewiston - Dedication of Lewiston-Queenstown Bridge 2. Luncheon with Bridge Commission 3. Buffalo - Dedication of the General William J. Donovan State Office Building 4. Rochester - Meeting with County Chairman 5. Monroe County Republican Committee Dinner
  - Regrets, June 1963 (Box 13, Folder 432)
    1. Young Republican National Convention 2. American Guild of Variety Artists 3. Commencement Address Requests a. Hartwick College b. Skidmore College c. Union College d. Peekskill Military Academy 4. Oneida County Republican Committee 5. American Jewish Committee 6. Adelphi College 7. Skaneateles House and Garden Tour 8. Polyclinic Medical School 9. New Windsor Bicentennial Celebration 10. Detroit Jewish Community Dinner 11. Governor's Day at Camp Drum 12. National Paper Mill Superintendents 13. Women's Convention Auxiliary of the New England Baptist Missionary Convention 14. Nassau County Federation of Republican Women 15. Kiwanis Club of Utica 16. Century Club Dinner 17. National Federation of High School Athletic Associations
  - Albany, New York, July 1, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 433)
    1. Regional Urban Transportation Planning
  - Massena, New York, July 15, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 434)
    1. New York State Society of Newspaper Editors
  - Idlewild Airport, New York, July 16, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 435)
    1. Meeting with Federal Aviation Authority (FAA) Officials
  - San Francisco, California, July 26-28, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 436)
    1. Bohemian Club Encampment
  - New York, New York, July 30, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 437)
    1. American Veterinary Medical Association
  - Regrets, July 1963 (Box 14, Folder 438)
    1. Orleans County Republican Committee 2. Dedication of Northway, Saratoga County 3. Long Island Summer Festival of the Arts
  - Elmira, New York, August 2, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 439)
  - Goshen, New York, August 6, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 440)
    1. Orange County republican Women's Tea (Margaretta Fitler Rockefeller attended, not NAR)
  - Little Rock, Arkansas, August 7, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 441)
    1. Dinner in honor of Winthrop Rockefeller
  - Saratoga, New York, August 17, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 442)
    1. The Traverse Stakes
  - Rhinebeck, New York, August 20, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 443)
    1. Dutchess County Fair Opening
  - New York, New York, August 27, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 444)
    1. Long Island Rail Road Commuter Cars Delivery
  - Albany, New York, August 28, 1963; Syracuse, New York, August 28, 1963; Syracuse, New York, August 29, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 445)
    Albany 1. Swearing-in Ceremony of John Lomenzo as Secretary of State Syracuse - August 28 1. State Farm Dinner Syracuse - August 29 New York State Fair 1. "SPICE" (poultry association) Breakfast 2. Tour of New York State Fair
  - Regrets, August 1963 (Box 14, Folder 446)
    1. St. Lawrence County Fair 2. Holy Name Convention 3. Western Kirkville Bar-B-Cue 4. New York State Fire Fighters Association
  - New York, New York, September 2, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 447)
  - New York, New York, September 4, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 448)
    1. American Political Science Association
  - Illinois, September 7, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 449)
    1. Press conference 2. Reception 3. 16th Congressional District Picnic 4. Dartmouth Club of Rockford Reception
  - New York, New York, September 10, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 450)
    1. Outdoor Concert, Bowling Green
  - Denver, Colorado, September 14, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 451)
    1. Republican Governor's Association
  - New City, New York; Kingston, New York, September 16, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 452)
    New City 1. Dedication, Rockland-Tarrytown Shuttle Bus Kingston 1. Ulster County Republican Committee
  - Glens Falls, New York, September 17, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 453)
    1. Washington and Warren Counties Dinner
  - West Virginia, September 21, 1963; Virginia, September 22, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 454)
    West Virginia 1. Visit Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Veterans Employees Association 2. Press conference 3. Federation of Republican Women's Luncheon 4. Republican Workshop Conference 5. Republican Reception 6. West Virginia Republican Finance Committee Virginia 1. Motorcade from Airport to Roanoke 2. Virginia Municipal League Dinner
  - Regrets, September 1963 (Box 14, Folder 455)
    1. Harlem Branch of Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) 2. Hebrew Home for the Aged in Riverdale 3. National Association of Furniture Manufacturers 4. Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) Century Club Dinner 5. Men's Club of Temple Beth-El 6. Town of Ohio (New York) Republican Club 7. Lincoln League of Monroe County
  - Brussels, Belgium, October 1, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 456)
    1. Opening of New York State Department of Commerce Office
  - Rochester, New York, October 5, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 457)
    1. National Conference of Editorial Writers
  - New York, New York, October 6, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 458)
  - Liberty, New York, October 8, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 459)
    1. Industrial Growth Conference
  - New York, New York, October 10, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 460)
    1. Western Hemisphere Day Dinner
  - Indiana; Oregon, October 12, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 461)
    Indiana 1. Indiana Bar Association Oregon 1. Press conference 2. Republican Western Conference Luncheon 3. University of Oregon vs. Idaho football game
  - New York, New York; Buffalo, New York, October 14, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 462)
    New York City 1. Interview with Walter Cronkite, CBS-TV Buffalo 1. United Steel Workers of America
  - Pocantico Hills, New York, October 15, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 463)
    1. Westchester Day at the Rockefeller family estate
  - New York, New York, October 16, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 464)
    1. Opening Ceremonies - New York World's Fair 2. Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation Dinner
  - New Hampshire, October 18-19, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 465)
    October 18 1. Press conference 2. Lunch with State Republicans 3. University of New Hampshire Young Republicans 4. Formal Address, University of New Hampshire October 19 1. Colby Junior College, remarks 2. Hanover 3. Dartmouth University Class of '30 reunion 4. Dartmouth vs. Holy Cross football game
  - Brooklyn, New York, October 21, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 466)
    1. Empire Missionary Baptist State Convention
  - Western United States, October 22-24, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 467)
    October 22 - Salt Lake City, Utah 1. Press conference 2. Luncheon with Republican Leaders 3. Courtesy Call, Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints 4. University of Utah October 23 - San Francisco, California 1. Press conference 2. League of California Cities 3. Meeting with Republican Leaders October 24 - Los Angeles, California 1. Press conference 2. Town Hall luncheon 3. KNBC-TV taping 4. California Club private meeting 5. Republican Central Committee of Los Angeles
  - Kiamesha Lake, New York, October 26, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 468)
    1. Convention of the New York State American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO)
  - New York, New York, October 27, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 469)
    1. Dinner in honor of Laurance Rockefeller 2. Grand Council of Columbia Associations
  - New York, New York, October 28, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 470)
    1. National Paint, Varnish, and Lacquer Association, Inc. 2. Uniformed Fireman's Association
  - New York, New York, October 29, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 471)
    1. Association of the Bar of the City of New York 2. State Dinner honoring General Lucius Clay
  - Regrets, October 1963 (Box 15, Folder 472)
    1. New York State Wholesale Beer Distributors 2. National Council of Police Societies 3. Peace on Earth Good Will Toward All Men Award 4. National Potato Chip Festival 5. Dedication at Dutchess Community College 6. International Chapter, National Association of Housing and redevelopment Official (NAHRO) 7. International Institute Foundation 8. 32 Carat Club of Philadelphia 9. Jewish War Veterans of the United States 10. Cattaraugus County Republican Committee 11. National Stationery and Office Equipment Association 12. NSOEA Convention 13. Mount Vernon Senior High School 14. Dedication of new Mallory Headquarters 15. State University of New York at Buffalo 16. Children's Dental and Eye Clinic
  - Newburgh, New York, November 2, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 473)
    1. Dedication of Newburgh-Beacon Bridge 2. Luncheon, New York State Bridge Authority
  - New York, New York, November 6, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 474)
    1. Building and Construction Trades Council 2. The Pilgrims of the United States
  - Miami Beach, Florida, November 13, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 475)
    1. Associated Press Managing Editors Association 2. WCKT-TV, Town meeting 3. WLBW-TV, "Miami News Conference"
  - New York, New York, November 14, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 476)
    1. American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Constitutional Convention
  - St. Louis, Missouri, November 16-17, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 477)
    November 16 1. News conference 2. KMIX-TV, "Closeup" 3. KSD-TV, Interview with Mary Spencer 4. Republican National Committee Reception 5. Press Club of Metropolitan St. Louis Dinner November 17 1. KMOX-TV, "Face the Nation"
  - New York, New York, November 20, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 478)
    1. The Atomic Industrial Forum and the American Nuclear Society Conference
  - New York, New York, November 21, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 479)
    1. "A Tribute to Ken Keating" Dinner
  - New Hampshire, November 24-26, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 480)
    November 24 1. Manchester - Meeting with State Labor Leaders 2. Nashua - Country Club Reception for media November 25 1. Derry - Pinkerton Academy, speech 2. Derry - Main Street hand shaking 3. Conway - Shopping Center Tour 4. North Conway - Community Building hand shaking 5. Newport - Latchis Theatre, speech 6. Newport - Main Street hand shaking 7. Portsmouth Young Republican Club November 26 1. Peterborough - Historical Building tour 2. Keene - Thoreau Room reception 3. Keene - Hand shaking tour 4. Keene - Monadnock High School, speech
  - Scarsdale, New York, November 26, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 481)
    1. Westchester County Association
  - Regrets, November 1963 (Box 15, Folder 482)
    1. Girl Scout Nature Sanctuary 2. National Association of Real Estate Boards 3. Medical Staff of St. Clare's Hospital 4. Association of Industrial Advertisers 5. Republican "coffee" in Beacon 6. National Maritimes Trades Department 7. African Dinner Dance
  - New York, New York, December 2, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 483)
    1. State Traffic Safety Council
  - Baltimore, Maryland, December 4, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 484)
    1. Johns Hopkins reception (canceled)
  - Wilmington, Delaware, December 5, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 485)
    1. Rotary Club Luncheon (canceled)
  - New York, New York, December 7, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 486)
    1. The Pennsylvania Society (canceled)
  - Regrets, December 1963 (Box 15, Folder 487)
    1. Adelphia Academy Centennial Ball 2. City Club of Chicago
  - Albany, New York, January 7, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 488)
    1. Republican State Committee
  - Albany, New York, January 9, 1964; New Hampshire, January 9, 1964; Washington, DC, January 10, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 489)
    Albany 1. Republican Members of State Assembly New Hampshire 1. General Contractors Association Washington, D.C. 1. National Press Club 2. Meeting with National Labor Leaders 3. Maryland Rockefeller Organization
  - Albany, New York, January 14, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 490)
    1. New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum 2. New York State Association for Mental Health 3. New York State Women's Council
  - Albany, New York, January 15, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 491)
  - New Hampshire, January 16, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 492)
    1. Keene - Monadnock High School 2. Keene - Keene Teachers College 3. Keene - Reception and tour of downtown 4. Peterborough - Reception and tour 5. Wilton High School - Reception 6. Milford - Tour of plant 7. Derry - Reception and dinner 8. Manchester - Rockefeller Headquarters
  - Boston, Massachusetts, January 22, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 493)
    1. Press conference 2. Dartmouth Alumni Association
  - Washington, DC; New York, New York, January 23, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 494)
    Washington, D.C. 1. New York Young Republicans 2. Young Republican Training School New York City 1. Westchester Republican County Committee Dinner
  - New Hampshire, January 24, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 495)
    1. Laconia - Chamber of Commerce 2. Tour of several towns 3. Concord a. Meeting with Governor King b. File Petition for primary c. Reception and Dinner
  - New York, New York, January 25, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 496)
  - Buffalo, New York, January 27, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 497)
    1. County Officers Association
  - California, January 28-30, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 498)
    January 28 - San Francisco 1. Press conference, at airport 2. Business Leaders Luncheon 3. Northern California Campaign Committee 4. Northern California Headquarters Opening 5. Marin County - Reception 6. Train trip to Los Angeles January 29 - Los Angeles 1. Negro College Alumni Leaders breakfast 2. Press conference 3. Business Leaders Luncheon 4. Southern California Headquarters Opening 5. United Republican Finance Committee January 30 - Los Angeles 1. Southern California Campaign Committee Breakfast 2. ABC-TV taping 3. Long Beach - Luncheon
  - Nashua, New Hampshire, January 31, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 499)
    1. Opening of campaign headquarters 2. Chamber of Commerce dinner